Hell Pace! Hell Pace! Dream Safe!
Hell Pace !Hell Pace!
Hell Pace!
Give those back!
You'll pay for this!
AAMH!
HUM! HUM!
HUM!
A-A-A-A-A!
You're Sabo, right?
Huh? Wait a sec.
You're Joey Bonnie.
If you know who I am, then
that saves us some time.
I think we have the same goal.
Intruders in the guard room!
They've stolen the keys
to the slave's colors!
Kill them on sight!
I knew Kuma had a
daughter, but that's all.
We've never met before, but I've been
keeping up with your group for a while.
Point is, I know you guys are my allies,
and I trust you to save my dad! We will.
That's what we're here for.
Karasu! I'm here.
I found the keys.
Take them and tell the other captains.
Once you rescue Kuma and unlock the
slave callers, go straight back to HQ.
Your mission will be complete.
We don't have much time.
Go, and hurry!
What about you, Sabo?
I'll be all right.
I'll follow once I finish my business.
Got it. Be careful!
I assume you'll be leaving soon.
What's next?
I'll be going straight to Egghead.
I'll by yourself?
Uh-huh.
You sure that's smart?
It's world government territory.
It doesn't matter!
I need Vegapunk to restore my dad's mind!
That's the whole reason
I went to see. Hold on.
Do you really think he can
get Kuma back to normal?
Well, I'm not leaving until he does it.
So he'd better fix them, or else.
There they are! This way! Hurry!
Where are they? Damn it. They're gone.
How strange.
I could have swore I saw someone.
Thanks.
Nice timing.
Why do they insist on making
things so difficult for us?
There simply aren't enough guards in this
tower to patrol a space as large as this.
What?
Surely you must have heard.
We're short on manpower because of...
you know what? Pardon?
Apparently they saw it. Saw what?
The lost chamber.
Keep your voice down, you fool.
Don't even joke about that.
Thanks, Sabo. Well,
Egghead is in the new world, so it looks
like we're headed in opposite directions.
Just be careful. Okay.
I'll keep you in my thoughts.
Huh?
Thanks, but this is weird. Yeah?
You're not a pirate like me.
Don't know how I feel about a
revolutionary treating me nice.
We both want to save Kuma, right?
Hmm.
Get him back safe.
What do you wish to ask,
Cobra King of Alabasta?
Speak up!
Well, I suppose I should
start at the beginning.
It is said that roughly 800 years ago,
there were 20 monarchs who came together
to form the world government as we know it.
After creating this new regime, they
relocated their families to Mariejois.
Those families became known
as the Celestial Dragons,
and they have reigned for eight centuries.
But there was no supreme ruler.
They all shared their power equally.
The Empty Throne is a
monument to that commitment.
It symbolizes their promise to
never allow a dictator to reign.
The twenty monarchs placed
their weapons at its feet,
vowing that none would sit upon it.
Meanwhile, in their homelands,
new royal families were selected.
And those families have
been in power ever since.
Therefore, their names all differ
from those of the first twenty.
A new line of succession
was born in each nation.
And yet Alabasta is different.
Queen Lily of the
Nefertari family was named
one of the first twenty
monarchs at the time.
But she did not become a celestial dragon.
She returned to Alabasta.
And we, the Nefertari family,
still reign there to this day.
I assume that is the reason there are only
nineteen weapons surrounding the throne.
What you've said is correct,
but what is your point?
Well, I've been perusing some
old books we have in my country.
Of course, none of those texts
predate the Void century,
so we cannot know the full truth.
But I still notice something odd.
Lily is missing.
Her name is nowhere to be found.
It would seem she never made it
back to the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Her younger brother ruled
the country in her stead.
Nothing else about her fate was written.
Could you tell me what
you know about that?
Is that all you wish to ask?
About an 800-year-old story?
As you said,
the monarch of the Nefertari family
did not choose to stay like the others.
But the belief was that she
returned to her country.
No one knows why she left
or where she ended up.
Those details have been lost to time.
That is all we know, I'm afraid.
Then what is the D?
And why would you ask that?
It's quite brief, but there is a letter
that Queen Lily wrote 800 years ago.
Our family has passed it
down for generations now.
Ah! No!
Let it go!
I'm begging you!
Please stop!
Don't do this! Please!
Please!
You're hurting me!
This isn't right!
Somebody stop him!
It was hard work, but I finally did it!
I never gave up on my dream!
And now the giant mermaid belongs to me!
Good lad! She's all yours! The fine catch!
Please, someone help!
He's going to take me away!
This is a nightmare!
Oh, my poor sweet Shirahoshi!
Oh, I wonder what I should feed her.
I can't wait for her to
pick me up with her big,
beautiful hands and carry
me around town all day.
Look at my new pet, Shirahoshi.
Now stop looking and get out of my way.
Everyone loves me.
And if you don't obey me, I'll be
sure to give you help. I refuse.
Why won't anyone help?
Why are you just watching?
Please save me!
Why now?
My father and all our guards
are in the council tower.
He doesn't own me!
This isn't right!
It seems there's only one option.
You'll help me?
Run away, hurry!
Oh, no!
You mermaid!
Are you being rebellious already?
I should have you flinch!
Honestly, it's rude of her
to expect us to bail her out!
She turned us down!
We can turn down saving
her from slavery, right?
That's right!
I won't put my neck on the
line for her! Make way!
You pathetic, filthy cowards
are as spineless as a jellyfish!
Ah!
The princess!
Oh, you can't fight!
They'll destroy your whole country!
Sister, forgive us for
letting this happen!
I'm so glad you're here!
I just wish we'd come
sooner, but you're safe now.
We'll set you free right away.
Let's return home.
We'll never come to
this cursed place again.
Thank you for commotion.
Oh, you're going home?
That sounds like a splendid idea to me.
The mermaid stays as my pet,
and you get out of my hair.
I don't want any fish, men.
You bastard!
Give her back!
How dare you treat her that way!
You pay for this! Yes!
Kill them, Kuma!
My invincible space!
Don't kill them, please!
Shirahoshi!
Rebecca!
We'll get those chains off of you!
It's that creep again!
I don't care who he is, we'll stop him!
Just checking you, Skyev, but I
can kick his ass this time, right?
Of course!
I'll take full responsibility for it!
A pity that a former warlord has been
reduced to this, but I won't relent! Forward!
Let's go!
Ryuboshi! Mamboshi! Ready!
Just kill them, Kuma!
It'll be fine!
Even if they are royalty, there's no
problem a little money can't solve.
They are just fish.
How dare you!
Please calm down!
You mustn't forget your royalty!
Don't stop me!
Leave it to them instead!
Our sister is in trouble!
I can't just watch!
Why do they have a right
to step up when we don't?
Because they are pirates!
Think of your country!
You could start a war!
Damn you, Miosgaard!
Don't you dare think I forgot
the insult you dealt to me!
Come on, kill Mulescarp this instant!
Slug dragon calls me!
I'll show the techniques drill dragon!
Sir Lee!
Sir Sly!
Don't do it!
He'll put you to death!
Kill him!
And I fail!
Chalos!
They killed him!
Oh, the inhumanity!
This is murder!
The murder of a celestial dragon!
Someone call the admirals now!
Stop it, Kuma!
Please don't do this!
We came here and I set you free!
Okay?
You don't have to follow
their orders anymore!
We can help you!
Let's go home together!
What is a giant doing here?
Morley!
I got the keys from Sabo! Come on!
What is that? An intruder!
That's Morley, a captain
of the Revolutionary Army!
Going down! See ya!
Oh, my son!
What have they done to you?
Great Emu!
King Cobra is still here!
Did he say Imu?
Lily...
No one is meant to sit upon that throne.
The world should not bend
to one person's will.
This was the oath.
There are two things
that I wish to tell you.
And one thing I wish to ask of you, Cobra.
But who are you?
The name Emu sounds familiar.
Surely it's a coincidence.
But among the first twenty, there was...
Cease your prying.
I will not respond to it.
But I shall answer your previous question.
The D you speak of is the name of
those who once opposed us long ago.
It has reared its ugly head
rather frequently in recent years,
among hollow shells who don't even
know the meaning of their own name.
That wretched faction, like
so many other scourges,
stemmed from Queen Lily's
great mistake 800 years ago.
What mistake?
we have her to thank
for those scholars who
were sniffing around
the void century as well
and for the pirates who
seek for the poneglyphs
and their never-ending search for treasure
were it not for lily's mistake on that
fateful day those stones would never have
been scattered across the world and not
a soul would covet the lonesome things
a damning question must be asked was
this travesty an accident were the
poneglyphs truly unleashed upon the
world by mistake or was it all by design
I believe you know the answer.
It must have been written in Lily's
letter that arrived in Alabasta.
I cannot help but notice
that you have referred
to her only as Queen Lily
of the Nefertari family.
Why is that?
What is the proper name
written on that letter?
Say it.
That settles it.
My hopes were already dwindling.
But now I'm certain I won't
be leaving this room alive.
If I renounce the truth,
then would you let me go?
Your fate was sealed the moment
you laid eyes on Great Emu.
A lie will change nothing.
Of course it won't.
I've uncovered the greatest
secret in the world.
What's going on in there?
Something is very wrong.
The letter that you speak of was signed
by the Queen of Alabasta 800 years ago.
Her full name was...
Nefertari.
D. Lily.
D.
FIREFIST!
Look check!
Where did you come from?
Seems it was naive of me to
think I could take you down.
I didn't expect to find hell up
here at the top of the world.
You stay away!
Young man, you're him, aren't you?
Luffy's brother.
You're a revolutionary.
Why would you protect a king?
Our true enemies are the
ones who sit above the kings.
These monsters.
But wait, how do you know Luffy?
Well, he saved my life.
Sounds like him.
I know it hurts, but hold on.
I'm gonna do my best to get you out...
You won't escape with me slowing you down.
I'm going to die either way!
Please just leave me. Not a chance!
I've discovered something important.
No matter what!
I need you to leave here alive.
You have to pass on a message to Luffy.
and Vivi for me.
If you say so, but what is it?
Tell them that we all share the name D.
It can't be a coincidence, right?
What do you mean? What can't?
You both have the same...
They're done!
Looks tasty!
Hey, you can't eat two
at once. Yeah, I can.
I'm hungry.
He means they won't fit in your face.
Huh, mmm, yummy!
Well, okay then.
Wow, that's great.
Anyway, what were you about to say, Sabo?
Oh, I was just about to ask,
how come both of you guys' names
have the letter D in the middle? D?
Monkey D.
Ruthie and Pork Ass D. H.
There's a D in both.
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
I don't know why, but
who cares about names?
You want a D too, Sabo?
Huh?
Sa-di-bo?
Come on, don't put it there.
And who's gonna stop me?
Your name's Sa-di-bo!
Finally, I see the path forward
that Alabasta must take.
Don't die! Just hang on!
We're gonna get you through this, okay?
King Cobra
King Cobra!
The Poneglyphs...
...bear the flag of a new dawn.
Nefertari tea lily.
I'm counting on you!
I'm counting on you, Zeff.
King Cobra!
You must live on.
I'll see you
next time.
I'll
see
you
next time.